{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720078593","data":{"timestamp":" 947720078592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720079689","data":{"timestamp":" 947720079689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720080869","data":{"timestamp":" 947720080869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720082468","data":{"timestamp":" 947720082468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720095138","data":{"timestamp":" 947720095138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720096829","data":{"timestamp":" 947720096828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720099428","data":{"timestamp":" 947720099428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720107491","data":{"timestamp":" 947720107491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720118261","data":{"timestamp":" 947720118261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720121040","data":{"timestamp":" 947720121040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720129405","data":{"timestamp":" 947720129405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720131670","data":{"timestamp":" 947720131670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_lu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947720132365","data":{"timestamp":" 947720132364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_023419"," gameId":" 0dd9f3f8-26e4-4e40-8fee-a35ed79d3e2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}